trying to scope is anyway like to return
yeah
no shelling in this periscope
goodbye to friends oh that that was
misleading
what goodbye to friends saying goodbye
to it doesn't matter so just ride
goodbye to floor I wrote saying goodbye
to friends I yeah that's good man
but that's pretty misleading no it's not
why is it misleading because like they
could think little really saying goodbye
to them cuz they're its clickbait relax
it gets more people to watch the scope
ease I learned that from Logan Paul
focus that's true focus guys yeah but no
we're just talking this is a nice car
it's really nice
this white leather yeah it's so soft
they did something to the cow man who
just touched this
I know it's so this record is no way
gonna be this is such a pleasant car
like you look in it and you feel happy I
enjoy driving this car and you heard
that driving this car not sitting fine
but you know why we're trading it in
yeah we heard about this great piece of
open-source software called open pilot
which will drive your car for you you
guys heard of it yeah and it doesn't
work with Ford's yeah it only works with
on doesn't Toyota's we're trading in for
a hot
the cruise control what's your level of
a quarter beginning oh it's true of
course we never do anything cheap um but
guys this Ford was going away that's
pretty sad if you guys have any last
things to say we should have just said
saying goodbye to friend friend yeah it
is one friend yeah if I could figure out
how to pair my phone quickly we could
listen to great songs about loss I know
some great ones whoa whoa well let's not
go crazy you know connect a glitch
you're right there
yeah but then like you know you can't
you can't yeah yeah virtually Chris
yeah guys but I hope you enjoyed
watching this for Drive deaf when we go
home
can we take a montage of our periscope
yeah
the buying before do you guys remember
episode 10 of Pokemon where Ash almost
says goodbye to Pikachu they have this
song oh we should have played that
closing time by Green Day that's your
traditional good fact that closing time
is by Semisonic it's not it is it's semi
song because it's absolutely green day I
might we might both be wrong I really
don't think it's green the closing time
is Green Day is that what this copy
someone just said not Green Day
absolutely closing time
Wow everyone sing it's not I think it is
it's definitely but green they covered
it it's any sonic
time of our lives
time never clear made wonderful they're
all the same songs all the gde
F court no G Dec corporation you're
right it's me minor it's you hit that F
sharp G sharp is vulgar and the G chord
yeah but it is all G minor C yeah yeah
that's great song by the way yeah guys
the Ford oh man you guys don't even know
about the Ford drama where I broke the
door oh yeah fix that we fixed it it fit
any Ford dealership or for the
dealership that we're going to if you're
watching it's fixed so don't worry about
it it's done the ASME certified mechanic
sure you guys know that George drives in
one lane he never switches lanes
cuz it's dangerous yeah but I just
really started to realize we surgeries
how I don't change you ever change Lane
because it's dangerous sometimes you
change lanes when you get annoyed but
always that was doing the minimum lane
changes to get to Burns just notice how
I keep the craziest following distance I
try but very safe driver
yes I've driven a lot and I don't want
to die did you guys have a 3d printer
naming poor dead
Oh what was the winner I'm worried that
chase chase chase is coming to work for
us
it was really pretty boy but this is a
sad periscope we're going to say goodbye
to friends yeah friend friend
bad words
there's just no way you can be honest
did you do the New York Times thing yeah
it really lets you quantify how much of
a Johnny or how much were you I was when
he went down 20 percent I became along I
got it to the one point where I could
some time here yah yah is rhyming like I
think you could train your hearing
totally incredible well like it's like
what Chris is telling us if you look
here the Yanni like
just shows how your brain is scamming
you first part thank you
it's freezing
the scope is saying that or no but it's
very cold
the lane keep assist system just went
off at an absolutely random time those
great trading is a scam what your brain
is scamming you yeah why dude it's like
the one thing that's not scanning your
brain is totally scamming your why does
some time your audience I'm very here
long I never hear Yanni my brain is not
scamming them change the slider and find
the absolute critical Yanni Laurel I did
but at that point like when I changed
the slide I was just clear that these
people were hearing weird things and
that it was no longer true Wow remember
when we bought this for this can be part
of the montage look at the Ford
dealership dude remember too much do
they hate us
we're here to trade we've gotten so many
cars in the past year I really liked
like this car you used to be your
favorite it's still kind of is do we
have to get rid of that kind of yeah
it's all about focus
it's not the year of the for they don't
even sell these anymore no the year of
the Ford was short-lived those false
enthusiasm well we could still go to
babies r us were you offended by that
guy sitting no the road yeah that's a
good line
focus they're not the Ford Focus Honda
like that is about to see this is
acceleration advanced but it's
unnecessary there's a red light that
you're coming to wear but it's that's a
hybrid to work and now you have to like
really Jones yeah I lost no energy there
was no need to get here faster cuz now
we're just sitting at the red light now
even more pleasant to roll through we
should abuse this car before me baby
then we drop it I really don't drive
maybe you just yeah you're unbelievably
safe driver
yeah but you have to fit a lot so you
really do have to be a safe driver
that's right we've gone across the
steering controller for the awkward guys
is it the same as a second
they don't know Oh sister Jesus well
Jesus enemy too so nice
[Music]
it's bringing us to
the line
[Music]
yep virtually Chris you can email me
about my key pad for sure
[Music]
alright scobie's we leave you there